It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's a family guy
Hey, where's Cleveland?
Doesn't he have a relative in town
or something?
I don't know, but I ordered him a beer,
and now it's just sitting there
looking lonelier than
Alan Rickman's answering machine.
Hello. You've reached Alan Rickman
at 555-0122.
Please leave a message at the beep.
Hello, Alan Rickman. It's Alan Rickman
reminding you to move the pork chops
from the freezer to the refrigerator
so they defrost properly.
Do not disappoint me.
Hello. You've reached Alan Rickman
at 555-0122.
Please leave a message at the beep.
Alan, it's me again.
Remember that turtle joke for the party.
Hey, y'all. I want you to meet my cousin
from Jamaica, Madame Claude.
Nice to meet you all.
You sound like the crab
from Little Mermaid.
I had crabs once. It's awful. You got to buy
that cream that comes with a little comb.
Of course I can still use the comb.
- Well, that's Quagmire.
- And you know what else?
Madame Claude is psychic. She can
tell you what you were in a past life.
I already know what I was. A strawberry.
It's another pleasant day for me,
Peter the Strawberry.
Hey, Mr. Worm.
I welcome your arrival,
'cause we're all part of the same garden.
Wait. What are you... Wait, hey.
Hey, get out of here! Hey!
He was my neighbor and he violated me.
Now I'll never end up in a fancy pie!
What do you say, Joe? You want
your past life read? It'll be fun.
Sure. Why not?
Okay, dear.
Close your eyes and clear your mind.
Okay. I'm seeing something.
Joe, you were an octopus.
Yes! Yes, this is so awesome! Damn it!
Oh! That's so cool! That's so cool!
Do me next.
I'm getting something. I see you in London.
I think it's the 1800s. Oh, my!
You were Jack the Ripper!
Giggity!
- What about Peter?
- Yeah, Peter next!
I don't think there's anything
in that black bag for me.
You're wrong, Peter. Let us begin.
Oh, my! You were a very important man.
You were Griffin Peterson,
the founder of the city of Quahog.
Now, wait a second, Cool Runnings.
We learned in school
that Miles "Chatterbox" Musket
founded Quahog
after he was saved by the magic clam.
No, that is a myth.
Peter, you were the founder of Quahog.
I see... I see England a long time ago.
It is a crisp, clear spring morning,
and Griffin Peterson is riding
to the home of his beloved.
Peterson, what are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be down at your job making
oblong bricks out of manure and straw?
No, we're off. It's Martin Luther Day.
Yes, that's a very smart joke.
Isn't that right, comedy professors?
Well done. Indeed.
- Now, what do you want?
- I want to marry your daughter,
and I'm here to ask for your blessing.
What could you possibly have
to offer my daughter?
Well, I'm one of the few guys in this town
who isn't dying
a slow, painful diarrhea death.
All right, come on in.
Knock-knock. Lady Redbush?
Griffin! It's so good to see you.
I'm so horny. Kiss my hand.
What are you doing here?
I was just walking off
the rotted goose anus I had for breakfast,
and I thought I'd come by
and ask you a little question.
- What's that?
- Will you marry me?
Oh, my God, yes!
Yes, I will, Griffin!
Oh, I thought you'd never ask.
- Did you do it?
- I did it!
But in another part of London,
there was a man
who was not in such good spirits.
The King of England, Stewart the Third.
I'm so bored. I wish to be entertained.
Where's my troupe of actors?
Presenting the cast of
How I Met Your Mother!
- You told her I told you I kissed her?
- Dude, you broke the bro code.
That's not against the bro code.
Yes, it is. Article 15 B.
That's the heart of the bro code, man.
Whoa, you're right!
I guess I did break the bro code.
Hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa... What is this?
Are these jokes? Do people
in other castles think this is funny?
Well, yeah. We get a pretty sizeable chunk
of princes 18 to 34.
I think I'd like to delete this from my TiVo.
Are you sure you want
to delete this program?
Yes.
Bring me my mid-season replacement fool!
- Hi there.
- I want to hear some jokes, fool!
Well, you know, I don't really tell jokes.
I like to tell stories from my life
and let the humor just flow organically
from everyday situations.
Yeah, my aunt Frieda was a real card.
She always had the most wonderful spirit,
even when her mind started to go.
I remember once she wrote a letter
to my Uncle Tom,
from whom she'd been divorced
for several years.
And in the letter,
she misspelled his name T-O-M-M.
And I said, "Frieda,
you've spelled Tom's name wrong.
"You need to take out one of the'M's. "
And she said, "Which one?"
You know, you're gonna be fucking dead
in five seconds
if Aunt Frieda doesn't throw a pie
at somebody!
I mean, part of that is you sort of
have to know my...
- Make me laugh!
- Hey, look. Keys.
That's so satirical!
What social commentary!
Well, now I'm in a wonderful humor.
I wish to go for a walk into town.
Hey, coachman, let's drive on the left side
of the road and see if that catches on.
Good Lord! Who is that?
That's Lady Redbush
and her husband-to-be, Griffin Peterson.
That piece of ass is marrying
that tall glass of poop juice?
Well, not if I have anything to say about it.
A woman of that caliber
should be married to a king.
Well, what are you gonna do about him?
I'm the king, jester. I'm going to have him
exiled to the farthest corner of the world.
And then she'll be all mine!
Why is he such a jerk to everybody?
Because he has a very, very small penis.
I've seen it, actually,
and it's, like,
you don't even want to make fun of it.
You know, it's just medically fascinating.
I kind of want to see it.
Yeah, it's like that one grape in the bunch
that never got to be a grape.
- I wonder what's keeping Griffin?
- I'm sure he'll be along, sweetie.
Remember, he's tubby.
It takes him a while to move around.
- I hope he didn't get diarrhea and die.
- Can I feel those boobs?
- No! Daddy! What are you? Sick?
- Hey, it's a different time!
What a wonderfully exciting day!
I'm young, I'm all dressed up,
and I'm on my way to marry
the woman I love.
And there's 290 years separating me
from the films of Kevin Smith.
Hey, Peterson.
- Who are you?
- I'm King Stewart.
- Don't you recognize me from the coins?
- Oh, yeah. The ones with your profile.
You know,
you look really weird from the side.
Well, that's something we didn't really
think out too well when we started.
But never mind that!
You're going into exile, Peterson!
I'm shipping you out on the first boat
to the New World!
But I'm supposed to get married today.
Oh, Yeah? Where are you going
for your honeymoon?
- That medium-sized hill.
- Wrong! Seize him!
And King Stewart's
cruelty was only just beginning.
Maybe he changed his mind.
Maybe he's not coming.
Oh! Come on now.
There, feel better after I just said that?
- Now give me one little touch.
- No!
I hate this! I... I... I hate my life!
- The king!
- The king is here!
Oh, I didn't vote for him!
Your majesty, this is a real honor.
Carter Redbush. Very glad to meet you.
Hello. Harry MacAfee.
As a citizen,
I'm proud to have you reign over me
and the MacAfee Fertilizer Company.
Lady Redbush,
I wish I was here on a happier errand,
but I'm afraid I must inform you
that Griffin Peterson is dead.
What?
Now that some time has passed,
do you want to go out?
With Griffin Peterson
exiled to the New World
and Lady Redbush believing he was dead,
King Stewart was now free to marry her.
The bride and groom
have written their own vows.
Our love is like two figs hanging from
a fig tree cradled by Cupid's own hand.
You and I are like two...
Oh, uh, I'm sorry. Is my wedding
interrupting your, your promotion?
We're right in the middle of our show,
okay?
Right now. You have a time slot. Go there.
Maybe finish this candy bar
before you open another one!
Well, at least it wasn't one of those
promos where they've got the whole cast
shoving each other playfully
like they're all good pals.
Oh, oh, look! There we go! Oh!
Look at them jostling each other around!
Oh! They give each other a hard time,
but they're friends.
Is that a real show?
No, it's just... No.
Somebody's making a joke. Forget it.
Meanwhile,
Griffin Peterson and the other exiles
pass the time on the ship
to the New World.
Aw, crap! A splinter.
Well, it's been nice knowing you guys.
So what'd you do to get exiled?
I got caught pleasuring myself
to a painstakingly etched engraving
of the Wife of Bath. What'd you do?
I slept with an underage virgin
to cure my puff penis.
Hey, fellows. You want to join me
in a game of mumble peg?
- Oh, no, thanks.
- Fine. I'll play by myself.
One, nothing!
Eventually, after many months at sea,
Griffin Peterson and his shipmates
finally reached the New World.
I declare this land Quahog!
This place is nothing but a wilderness!
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna build a new settlement.
We'll have a happy new life,
and we'll have equal rights for all.
Except blacks, Asians, Hispanics, Jews,
gays, women, Muslims...
Um... Everybody who's not a white man.
And I mean white-white.
So no Italians, no Polish.
Just people from Ireland, England
and Scotland.
But only certain parts of Scotland
and Ireland. Just full-blooded whites.
No, you know what? Not even whites.
Nobody gets any rights.
America.
How's your stewed fox quail, my dear?
It's quite good.
I'm also enjoying the turtled hen.
Isn't the turtled hen good?
So, listen,
you and I need to have a conversation
about you not bearing me a son.
Well, my lord, we've discussed this.
We have to have sex
in order for me to bear you a son.
Oh, I know. I've just been so tired,
and I've had so much work.
And I think... I think I wanted to
the other day but I couldn't find you.
So, you know, it's, like, both of us
and our schedules, you know?
Well, why don't we do it tonight?
Maybe. Tonight might work. Yeah...
Oh, no! I got that thing in the morning!
How about tomorrow at 4:00?
You know I'm with my mother
tomorrow at 4:00.
Darn it!
I'm gonna be so horny tomorrow at 4:00.
You know, I got to say I'm a little mad
at you for not being more available.
We can have sex right now on the table.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Hey. We eat here.
Griffin Peterson and the other colonists
worked day and night
to build their new settlement.
Until finally, after much hard work,
the colony of Quahog was complete.
It didn't take long before Quahog
was a thriving New World settlement
bustling with life.
Boy, everything's shaping up real nice!
Yeah, and we finally finished
the town abortion clinic.
Time had helped Griffin
forget Lady Redbush.
And soon he found himself
a hearty new wife.
Boy, that was fantastic!
You must have had a lot of practice.
No, not really.
I've been saving myself for marriage.
We should probably
open up some windows.
I don't know what to do, jester.
I can't be married to the king anymore.
My heart still belongs to Griffin Peterson,
but he's dead.
- No, he's not.
- What?
I was ordered to keep silent
by the king under threat of execution.
But you're gonna see this anyway.
Oh, my God! He's alive.
Jester, I've got to get to him.
I'll help you, but only if I can go with you.
If I stay here, the king
will execute me for telling you all this.
He's a real fit head.
Well, okay.
But how are we gonna get there?
We'll hitch a ride on one of the slave ships
tomorrow night
after an all-new Shovin'Buddies.
Followed by an all-new
Slowly Rotating Black Man.
And so Lady Redbush sailed off
to the New World to find her beloved,
and the timing was good because
his new wife was a pain in him ass.
And then I finished scrubbing the kettle,
but then I saw that I had missed a spot.
And, oh, I was so worried that
the whole thing wasn't clean enough,
so I went back
and started washing it again.
And sure enough, I'd missed another spot.
And there was a clump of cornmeal
under the rim from when I made breakfast.
Shut up, Meg! I pray thee, shut up.
- Griffin!
- Lady Redbush!
And so Griffin Peterson
and Lady Redbush were happily reunited.
Of course, Griffin had to go through
the complex, extensive divorce procedure
required by 18th century society.
Gone? What do you mean she's gone?
Sire, Lady Redbush
has been gone these six months.
- Six months?
- Yes. Forgive me, sire.
But how could you not be aware of this?
Don't you share a bedchamber with her?
Well, I mean, sometimes, I mean,
we sleep... We... We... We go to different...
We go to bed at different times.
We've both been so busy
it's been ridiculous.
I thought she was taking a class
or something.
Oh, man! That sucks because I'm so horny.
Damn it!
Oh... I wanted to do sex to her tonight.
- Well, then I guess we've got to go get her.
- Yeah. All right.
Months rolled by,
and Griffin and Lady Redbush continued
to flourish happily in the colony of Quahog,
completely unaware that King Stewart
was on the march.
There was a peaceful town called Quahog
Where people lived in harmony
They never had no kind of trouble
There was no hint of misery
Then all at once the trouble started
A pack of murderers and thieves
Like swarms of locusts they descended
Their aim to make the town folk flee
They've got to be here somewhere.
Where's my first lieutenant?
Here I am, sir. Yes, sir. Right indeed.
Here indeed. Yes, I am, sir!
I want you to turn this settlement
upside down
until you find Lady Redbush
and Griffin Peterson!
That fat bastard thinks he can steal
my bride and get away with it?
I wouldn't bet a corn farthing
on him escaping.
No, I wouldn't.
Not a corn farthing would I bet. No, sir.
- What's wrong with you?
- A little wrong in the head, I am,
from eating some bad sausages.
Yes, some bad sausages did I eat,
indeed, sir.
Yes, I did. Some bad sausages ate I.
Oh, Griffin, this time together has
been the happiest of my life.
Me, too, Lady Redbush.
All those months I was without you
I never stopped seeing your face
in the back of my wife's head.
And all those months
I was sailing for the New World,
I saw your face in every slave's stomach.
- Tell me we'll be together forever.
- We will.
I found him, Your Majesty.
Indeed, yes, I did found him, did I.
- Indeed, yes, sir. I did.
- Yeah, okay, okay. Whatever.
All right, Peterson,
two things are gonna happen here.
I'm gonna take my wife back,
and then I'm gonna kill you!
All right. All right, Mr. King, sir. You win.
I'm sorry, Lady Redbush,
but he is your husband.
Let me just walk over here
and get your things for you...
All right, Your Majesty.
If you want to leave
with your pal in one piece,
- I suggest you throw down your weapons!
- Ah!
Go ahead and kill him, Griffin!
You kill him and I'll kill her!
Go ahead! You kill her, I'll kill him!
Go ahead. You kill him, I'll kill her!
Knock yourself out.
You kill her, I'll kill him.
This is me laughing.
You kill him, I'll kill her!
This is me before
Ultra Slim-Fast. You kill her, I'll kill him!
Wait, wait! There's got to be
a better way to settle this!
- Talent show?
- Talent show.
"Hear ye. Hear ye. This talent competition
"will decide rightful possession
of the good Lady Redbush
"and control of the colony of Quahog. "
We first present King Stewart of England
with some observational humor.
Hi there, everybody.
You know, my Aunt Frieda was a real card.
She always had the most wonderful spirit,
even when her mind started to go.
What the fuck?
I remember once she wrote a letter
to my Uncle Tom,
from whom she'd been divorced
for several years.
And in the letter,
she misspelled his name T-O-M-M.
This is my bit. These are all my bits.
- This is funny.
- Unbelievable.
And I said, "Frieda,
you've spelled Tom's name wrong.
"You need to take out one of the'M's. "
And she said, "Which one?"
Clap your hands, everybody
And everybody clap your hands
We are the Quahog colonists
and Mort the Jew
Hey there
We're out here on stage tonight
to do a show for you
We got Peterson on the violin
And Quagmire and Joe will be joining in
We got stumpy Seamus on the lead guitar
And he's gonna give you a great big...
Break!
Oh, God,
they put so much work into theirs!
I didn't know we could rip off movies!
And from then on,
Lady Redbush and Griffin Peterson lived
in peace and happiness.
- Oh, Griffin, I love you.
- And I you.
Let's grow old into our 30s together.
I want to have a baby with you.
And I want to be there
when you die giving birth to it.
And so ends the tale of Griffin Peterson
and the founding of Quahog.
Well, what a bunch of delightfully
colorful characters! So, is that it?
That's it. Now stay tuned for an all-new
Crossarmed Opposites.
- This guy.
- No, this guy.
Both of us.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru